<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Black Arrow Gang</title><link>https://blackarrowgang.github.io/Landing/</link><description>Recent content on Black Arrow Gang</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:30:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blackarrowgang.github.io/Landing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Secure Access Made Simple: Terraform-driven AWS Client VPN</title><link>https://blackarrowgang.github.io/Landing/services/aws-vpn-client/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:30:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://blackarrowgang.github.io/Landing/services/aws-vpn-client/</guid><description>Secure Access Made Simple: Terraform-driven AWS Client VPN Description This repository provides a terraform code to set up an AWS infrastructure with a client VPN endpoint for secure remote access to resources within a VPC. It creates security groups to control access and establishes network associations for private subnets.
Use Cases The AWS VPN setup can be utilized in various scenarios, including:
Remote Access (Bastion Alternative): Provide a secure alternative to a bastion by enabling authorized users to securely connect with high availability to AWS resources through a virtual private network (VPN) from remote locations.</description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://blackarrowgang.github.io/Landing/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blackarrowgang.github.io/Landing/about/</guid><description>We are a rapidly growing Software development organization. Our team has the necessary expertise, zeal, and dedication, and we have helped a number of businesses achieve success and great performance.
We are an organization founded and run by Developers.
We operate as a team with an agile mindset.</description></item><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>https://blackarrowgang.github.io/Landing/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blackarrowgang.github.io/Landing/contact/</guid><description> Name Email Message</description></item></channel></rss>