<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Latest posts on Black Arrow Gang</title><link>https://blackarrowgang.github.io/Landing/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Latest posts on Black Arrow Gang</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 16:09:49 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blackarrowgang.github.io/Landing/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AWS Lambda Containers: A Game-Changer for Scalable and Efficient Serverless Applications</title><link>https://blackarrowgang.github.io/Landing/blog/aws-lambda-container/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 15:30:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://blackarrowgang.github.io/Landing/blog/aws-lambda-container/</guid><description>AWS Lambda Containers: A Game-Changer for Scalable and Efficient Serverless Applications Simplify the deployment of Docker containers as Lambda functions on AWS using Terraform. This code snippet creates a Lambda function module, and deploys a container image. Streamline your AWS Lambda deployment process and unleash the power of containerization with this efficient Terraform solution.
Table of contents Use Cases Requirements Installation Usage How It Works Support Use Cases Serverless Microservices: Deploy Docker containers as Lambda functions using Terraform to create serverless microservices architectures.</description></item><item><title>AWS RDS Proxy: Minimum Pricing High Flexibility</title><link>https://blackarrowgang.github.io/Landing/blog/aws-rds-proxy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 15:30:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://blackarrowgang.github.io/Landing/blog/aws-rds-proxy/</guid><description>AWS RDS Proxy: Minimum Pricing High Flexibility Boost your Amazon RDS databases with AWS RDS Proxy! Experience unrivaled scalability, availability, and security. With automatic connection pooling and failover mechanisms, managing your databases becomes a breeze. Eliminate manual scaling and unleash the true potential of your Amazon RDS infrastructure. Discover the game-changing power of AWS RDS Proxy today!
Use Cases Flexible Traffic Redirection: Provides exceptional flexibility for redirecting and distributing database traffic to accommodate evolving application requirements.</description></item><item><title>Simplify Remote Access: Effective AWS Client VPN Endpoint Setup</title><link>https://blackarrowgang.github.io/Landing/blog/aws-vpn-client/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 15:30:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://blackarrowgang.github.io/Landing/blog/aws-vpn-client/</guid><description>Simplify Remote Access: Effective AWS Client VPN Endpoint Setup AWS Client VPN Endpoint is a powerful solution that enables seamless and secure connectivity between remote users and AWS resources. With easy management and configuration, it provides a user-friendly experience for accessing sensitive data and applications.
Table of contents Use Cases Requirements Installation Usage How It Works Support Use Cases The AWS VPN setup can be utilized in various scenarios, including:</description></item><item><title>Scalable Database Cluster: AWS Aurora Serverless</title><link>https://blackarrowgang.github.io/Landing/blog/aws-serverless-rds-cluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 15:30:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://blackarrowgang.github.io/Landing/blog/aws-serverless-rds-cluster/</guid><description>Scalable Database Cluster: AWS Aurora Serverless Discover how Terraform, a powerful infrastructure-as-code tool, simplifies the process of deploying infrastructure on AWS. This blog post provides a concise overview of using Terraform to provision an AWS Serverless database cluster, and secure VPN access.
Use Cases The AWS RDS Aurora database cluster setup can be utilized in various scenarios, including:
Effortless Scalability for Startups: Startups effortlessly scale their databases with RDS Aurora serverless architecture and Terraform.</description></item></channel></rss>